A Guide to the Thomas H. Hunter Collection 1934-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1972, 5 TLS (Box-folder 28-17)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970, 5 TL (CC) (Box-folder 28-18)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970, 3 TL (P) (Box-folder 28-19)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970, TL (P), ALS (P) (Box-folder 28-20)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1968-1970, 8 TMs (P) (Box-folder 28-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1968-1971, 4 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 28-22)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1971, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 29-1)
  EDUCOM 1971-
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1971, 10 TLS (Box-folder 29-2)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1971, 8 TLS (P) (Box-folder 29-3)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1961, 6 TM (P) (Box-folder 29-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1971-1974, 7 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 29-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE 1971/ca, AN (Box-folder 29-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1971, 22 TMs (P) (Box-folder 29-7)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1972-1973, 5 TL (CC) (Box-folder 29-8)
  EDUCOM 1972-
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1973, 6 TLS (Box-folder 29-9)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1973, 7 TM (P) (Box-folder 29-10)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1975, 8 TLS (P), 4 TL (P) (Box-folder 29-11)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE 1972/ca, ANS (Box-folder 29-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1972-1975, 7 TMs (P) (Box-folder 29-13)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1972, 11 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 29-14)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974-1975, 3 TL (P) (Box-folder 29-15)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1956-1980, 43 TL (CC) (Box-folder 29-16)
  ELLIS, JOHN M.D.
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1955-1975, 21 TLS (Box-folder 29-17)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1956-1962, 11 ALS (Box-folder 29-18)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1980, 3 ALS (P) (Box-folder 29-19)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1958-1980, 5 TL (P) (Box-folder 29-20)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIALS 1956/ca, TMs (P), TMs (Box-folder 29-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS POSTCARD AND NOTE 1958/ca, APCS, AN (Box-folder 29-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT 1957, Reprint (Box-folder 29-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1972, 2 Reprints (Box-folder 29-24)
  Engineering 115
- ENGINEERING NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., 2 AMs (Box-folder 29-25)
- ENGINEERING 351 SYLLABUS 1973, TMs (P) (Box-folder 29-26)
- JAY SCHWARTZ TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971, TLS, TL (Box-folder 29-27)
  Engineering School Lectures
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971/05/06, TLS (P) (Box-folder 29-28)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972, 2 TM (P) (Box-folder 29-29)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972/03/13, TL (CC) (Box-folder 29-30)
- ENGINEERING SCHOOL LECTURE NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND 1972/ca, AMs, AMs (P) (Box-folder 29-31)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1972/ca, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 29-32)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1967-1971, 8 Reprints (Box-folder 29-33)
- MISCELLANEOUS PRINTED CARDS N.D., Printed Cards (Box-folder 29-34)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1976, 2 TLS (Box-folder 30-1)
  Engineering School Seminar Complex Systems
- MEMO SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/09/07, TM (P) (Box-folder 30-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1973/09/25, TMs (P) (Box-folder 30-3)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977-1978, 2 TLS (Box-folder 30-4)
  Ethical Analysis
- OLIVER WILLIAMSON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978/05/30, TMS (Box-folder 30-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1977, 14 Reprints (Box-folder 30-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIALS IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND 1977/ca, 2 AMs (Box-folder 30-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1972/ca, TMs (Box-folder 30-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1977-1978/ca, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 30-9)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT N.D., Reprint (Box-folder 30-10)
- ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES WEEKLY REPORT 1978/03/28, Newsletter (Box-folder 30-11)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE 1977/12/ca, AN (Box-folder 30-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1974-1976, TN, AN (Box-folder 30-13)
  Ethical Consultations
- NOTES ON ETHICAL CONSULTATIONS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975/07/10-23, TMsS, TMs (P) (Box-folder 30-14)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975/08/27, TL (CC) (Box-folder 30-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1968-1976, 13 Reprints (Box-folder 30-16)
- A LIVING WILL 1974/09, Pamphlet (Box-folder 30-17)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1965-1979, 57 TL (CC) (Box-folder 30-18)
  F File
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1979, 58 TLS (Box-folder 30-19)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1978, TLS, 2 TLS (P) (Box-folder 30-20)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1975, 2 TLS (P), TL (P), TL (CC) (Box-folder 30-21)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975-1976, 4 TM (P), TM (Box-folder 30-22)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO BILL 1967/10/26, ALS (P) (Box-folder 30-23)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969, 10 ALS (Box-folder 30-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1969-1976, 2 TMs, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 30-25)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 6 AN, TN (Box-folder 30-26)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1971, 3 TM (Box-folder 30-27)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1961-1980, 9 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 30-28)
- MISCELLANEOUS PATIENT RECORD 1952/ca, TMs (CC), AN (Box-folder 30-29)
  Family Planning
- BOOK ORDER FORM N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 30-30)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT AND PAMPHLET 1969, 2 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 30-31)
- HENRY S. WILLNER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975/03/11, TLS (Box-folder 30-32)
  Family Practice
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO HENRY S. WILLNER 1975/05/28, TL (CC) (Box-folder 30-33)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1970-1974, 2 Reprints (Box-folder 30-34)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1972/03/22, TMs (P) (Box-folder 30-35)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO DONALD NEUCHTERLEIN 1977, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 31-1)
  Federal Executive Institute
- DONALD NEUCHTERLEIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977, 2 TLS (Box-folder 31-2)
- CHONG M. PAK TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977/03/23, TL (CC) (Box-folder 31-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT AND PAMPHLET 1976-1977, 2 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 31-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSLETTERS 1963-1975, 8 Newsletters (Box-folder 31-5)
  Federation of American Scientists
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TLS (P) (Box-folder 31-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE N.D., AN (Box-folder 31-7)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1978-1981, 10 TL (CC) (Box-folder 31-8)
  FLETCHER, JOSEPH
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO MARTHA 1977-1978, 16 ALS (Box-folder 31-9)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARTHA 1977-1979, 29 TLS (Box-folder 31-10)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARY 1979-1980, 7 TLS (Box-folder 31-11)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978-1980, 42 TLS (Box-folder 31-12)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARTHA 1978, 3 ALS (Box-folder 31-13)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARY 1978/11/30, ALS (Box-folder 31-14)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981, 3 ALS (Box-folder 31-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 31-16)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977-1980, 9 TLS (P), TLS, ALS (P), 3 TLS (Box-folder 31-17)
- MRS. JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1979/ca, TN, ALS (Box-folder 31-18)
- PARKING FINE NOTICE 1977/09/20, TN (Box-folder 31-19)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND NEWSCLIPPINGS 1978-1980, 14 Reprints/Newsclippings (Box-folder 31-20)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JOSEPH FLETCHER 1976-1977, 9 TL (CC) (Box-folder 31-21)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARTHA 1976-1977, 6 TLS (Box-folder 31-22)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO MARY 1976/09/29, TLS (Box-folder 31-23)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER [1964]-1977, 15 TLS (Box-folder 31-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1956/ca, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 31-25)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977, TNS, ANS (Box-folder 31-26)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976-1977, TLS, TLS (P) (Box-folder 31-27)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIALS 1972/ca, 2 TMs (Box-folder 31-28)
  FLETCHER, JOSEPH REPRINTS AND PAPERS
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER; MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIALS 1973-1981, 5 TLS, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 31-29)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIALS 1972-1974, 12 TMs (P) (Box-folder 31-30)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JOSEPH FLETCHER 1980/04/24, TL (CC) (Box-folder 31-31)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1980/05/12, TLS (Box-folder 31-32)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1974, TLS, TLS (P) (Box-folder 31-33)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1973-1980, 22 Reprints (Box-folder 31-34)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1973, 5 TL (CC) (Box-folder 32-1)
  John E. Fogarty International Center
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, 7 TLS (Box-folder 32-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., 2 AMs (Box-folder 32-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1970-1973, 13 TMs (P) (Box-folder 32-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS 1970s/ca, 3 Pamphlets (Box-folder 32-5)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, 5 TM (P) (Box-folder 32-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1971-1973, 3 Reprints (Box-folder 32-7)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, 5 TLS (P) (Box-folder 32-8)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1965-1980, 53 TL (CC) (Box-folder 32-9)
  G File
- RUBY M. PAYNE TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1968, 4 TLS (Box-folder 32-10)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1980, 45 TLS (Box-folder 32-11)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1973, 16 ALS (Box-folder 32-12)
- PAUL GHALIOUNGUI TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968, 3 TLS (Box-folder 32-13)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 8 AN (Box-folder 32-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1967-1979, 10 Reprints (Box-folder 32-15)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965-1976, 27 TL/TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 32-16)
- SYMPATHY ACKNOWLEDGEMENT N.D., Printed Card (Box-folder 32-17)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPINGS 1968-1980, 3 Newsclippings (Box-folder 32-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS 1974-1975, 2 Pamphlets (Box-folder 32-19)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1974-1975, 9 TMs (P) (Box-folder 32-20)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1967-1968, 3 ALS (P) (Box-folder 32-21)
- MEMO SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977/02/15, TM (P) (Box-folder 32-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1942-1965, 10 Reprints (Box-folder 32-23)
  GALDSTON, IAGO
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1965-1981, 51 TL (CC) (Box-folder 33-1)
  GLASER, ROBERT J.
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965-1980, 64 TLS (Box-folder 33-2)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969-1976, 20 TL/TLS (P) (Box-folder 33-3)
- EDWARD H. KASS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972/01/19, TLS (Box-folder 33-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1968-1976, 5 Reprints (Box-folder 33-5)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1971, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 33-6)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1971, AN, 2 TLS (Box-folder 33-7)
- [ ] TO BOB 1970/04/22, ALS (P) (Box-folder 33-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1970-1972, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 33-9)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 2 AN (Box-folder 33-10)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO ROBERT K. GREENLEAF 1971-1976, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 33-11)
  GREENLEAF, ROBERT K.
- ROBERT K. GREENLEAF TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1974, 8 ALS (Box-folder 33-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1968-1974, 6 Reprints (Box-folder 33-13)
- MEMO SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/03/23, TM (P) (Box-folder 33-14)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, TL (P), TLS (P) (Box-folder 33-15)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1980-1981, 3 TLS (P) (Box-folder 33-16)
  GUERRANT, RICHARD L., M.D.
- RICHARD L. GUERRANT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1980/12/09, ALS (Box-folder 33-17)
- RICHARD J. CROSS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1980/11/21, TLS (Box-folder 33-18)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1980, 6 TLS (P) (Box-folder 33-19)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT 1980/11/19, Reprint (Box-folder 33-20)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1959-1981, 59 TL (CC), AL (Box-folder 33-21)
  H File
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1981, 44 TLS (Box-folder 33-22)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1976, 10 ALS (Box-folder 33-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE N.D., ANS (P) (Box-folder 33-24)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1977, 4 TLS (P) (Box-folder 33-25)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS [1912]-1974, 5 Reprints (Box-folder 33-26)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIALS 1974-1975, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 33-27)
- FRIENDSHIP FORCE MATERIALS 1980, TM (P), 3 Pamphlets/Printed Forms (Box-folder 33-28)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES AND POSTCARD 1976/ca, AN, TN, APCS (Box-folder 33-29)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971-1976, 5 TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 33-30)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1964-1971, 44 TL (CC) (Box-folder 34-1)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1969, 35 TLS (Box-folder 34-2)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1969, 6 TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 34-3)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1970, 20 ALS (Box-folder 34-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1966-1969, 3 Reprints (Box-folder 34-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPINGS 1967, 2 Newsclippings (Box-folder 34-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1966-1970, 7 TMs (P), 2 TMs (Box-folder 34-7)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1970, 19 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 34-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 3 AN (Box-folder 34-9)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1976-1977, 24 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 34-10)
  HADDEN, JEFFREY
- JEFFREY HADDEN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977/04/25, ALS (Box-folder 34-11)
- TODD C. HANSON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER; PROPOSAL 1979/02/13, TLS, TMs (P) (Box-folder 34-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1976-1977/ca, 7 AN (Box-folder 34-13)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO RICHARD J. BONNIE 1976/12/17, TL (CC) (Box-folder 34-14)
- GRANT PROPOSALS 1976-1977, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 34-15)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1977, 2 TM (Box-folder 34-16)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1974-1975, 6 TL (CC) (Box-folder 34-17)
  HARDIN, GARRETT
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974-1975, 3 TLS (Box-folder 34-18)
- GARRETT HARDIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1974, 3 ALS (Box-folder 34-19)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1979, 13 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 34-20)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974-1975, 2 TLS (Box-folder 34-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1968-1975, 23 Reprints (Box-folder 34-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1974-1981, 17 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 34-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPINGS 1972-1975, 14 Newsclippings (Box-folder 34-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 2 TN (Box-folder 34-25)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES AND LETTERS 1975/ca, 3 ALS (Box-folder 34-26)
- JOSEPH FLETCHER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975/07/25, TLS (Box-folder 34-27)
- INVOICES 1972, 4 Printed Forms (Box-folder 34-28)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1972-1975, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 34-29)
- NOTES RE GARRETT HARDIN BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 34-30)
- HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1960/06/11, Envelope (Box-folder 35-1)
  Harvard
- GEORGE PACKER BERRY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1960/06/11, TLS (Box-folder 35-2)
- HARVARD REPORT 1960/06, TMs (Box-folder 35-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS N.D., 2 Reprints (Box-folder 35-4)
- GEORGE PACKER BERRY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 3 TLS (Box-folder 35-5)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1963, 3 TL (CC) (Box-folder 35-6)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 35-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1961-1963, 2 Reprints (Box-folder 35-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1961, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 35-9)
- BOB TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962, 2 ALS (Box-folder 35-10)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1980, 21 TLS (Box-folder 35-11)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1967-1976, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 35-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1961-1965, 5 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 35-12)
- ALUMNI LISTINGS 1974-1980, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 35-13)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968-1980, 2 ALS, 2 TPCS (Box-folder 35-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND NEWSLETTERS 1966-1975, 6 Reprints/Newsletters (Box-folder 35-15)
- JEAN BRUNS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., 3 TM (Box-folder 35-16)
- MANUSCRIPT RE UVA MEDICAL SCHOOL BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TMs, AMs, TMs (P) (Box-folder 35-17)
- INVITATION 1976, Printed Invitation With Card (Box-folder 35-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS INVOICES, PAMPHLET, NOTE 1972-1973, Pamphlet, 3 Printed Forms, AN (Box-folder 35-19)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1974, 6 TL (CC) (Box-folder 35-20)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1975, 6 TL/TLS (Box-folder 35-21)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974, 5 TLS (Box-folder 35-22)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969-1974, 2 ALS (Box-folder 35-23)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO FRANK G. SOHN 1974/11/25, TLS (Box-folder 35-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1969-1970, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 35-25)
- RECEIPTS 1974, 7 Printed Forms (Box-folder 35-26)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSLETTERS 1970, 2 Newsletters (Box-folder 35-27)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1967-1975, 12 TL (CC) (Box-folder 35-28)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1973, 15 TLS (Box-folder 35-29)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967, 3 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 35-30)
- SUSAN P. KENYON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., APCS (Box-folder 35-31)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPING 1979/09/11, Newsclipping (Box-folder 35-32)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1969-1975, 20 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 35-33)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1971-1976, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 36-1)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1959-1980, 25 TLS (Box-folder 36-2)
- JOHN C. EWER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978/08/10, ALS (Box-folder 36-3)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1959-1964, 10 TM (P/CC) (Box-folder 36-4)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1959-1976, 10 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 36-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE AND RECEIPT N.D., TN, Printed Card (Box-folder 36-6)
- VISITING COMMITTEE REPORT BY THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., AMs, TMs (Box-folder 36-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1956-1974, 9 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 36-8)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1962-1964, 25 TL (CC) (Box-folder 36-9)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1965, 25 TLS (Box-folder 36-10)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1964, 10 TL (CC) (Box-folder 36-11)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1964, 4 TL (P) (Box-folder 36-13)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962, 2 TM (P) (Box-folder 36-14)
- PERRY J. CULVER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962/12/30, Telegram (Box-folder 36-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1959/12/19, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 36-16)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO PETER S. BING 1965/09/14, TL (CC) (Box-folder 36-17)
  Health Care
- PETER S. BING TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1965, 2 TLS (Box-folder 36-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1975-1976, 2 AN (Box-folder 36-19)
- MEMO AND CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975, 2 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 36-20)
- WHAT SOCIETY EXPECTS WITH RESPECT TO HEALTH CARE N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 36-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPINGS 1975, 4 Newsclippings (Box-folder 36-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1973-1975, 8 Reprints (Box-folder 36-23)
- MEMO AND MANUALS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962, TM (P), 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 36-24)
  Department of Health Education and Welfare (H.E.W.)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1963, 2 TLS (Box-folder 36-25)
- GRANT EVALUATIONS 1963, TMs (P) (Box-folder 36-26)
- DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, EDUCATION, AND WELFARE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., 3 Envelopes (Box-folder 36-27)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968, 2 TLS (Box-folder 37-1)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968-1975, 6 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 37-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1969/04/14, TMs (P) (Box-folder 37-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1969-1975, 4 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 37-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1968, TMs, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 37-5)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/03/22, TLS (P) (Box-folder 37-6)
- H. E. W. REFERENCE REQUEST 1970, 2 Prined Forms (Box-folder 37-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 2 AN (Box-folder 37-8)
- UNIDENTIFIED WOMAN N.D., Photograph, B&W; 8x10 (Box-folder 37-9)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1957-1967, 11 TL (CC) (Box-folder 37-10)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1957-1967, 19 TLS (Box-folder 37-11)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1967, 3 TL (CC) (Box-folder 37-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND NEWSLETTERS 1966-1967, 9 Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 37-13)
- H. E. W. NEWS RELEASE 1966/10/18, TMs (P) (Box-folder 37-14)
- R. BLACKWELL SMITH TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967/10/31, Telegram (Box-folder 37-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., 3 AN (Box-folder 37-16)
- H. E. W. CERTIFICATE N.D., Certificate (Box-folder 37-17)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO JOHN A. D. COOPER 1972/10/10, TL (CC) (Box-folder 37-18)
  Health and the Third World
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1977, 2 TLS (Box-folder 37-19)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1973-1979, 3 ALS (Box-folder 37-20)
- THELMA INGLES TO ANNE AND THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978/01/04, ALS (Box-folder 37-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1964-1977, 6 TMs (P) (Box-folder 37-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPTS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1978/ca, 2 TMs, TMs (P) (Box-folder 37-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1971-1981, 16 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 37-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPINGS 1972-1977, 2 Newsclippings (Box-folder 37-25)
- MEMO SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1981/06/05, TM (P) (Box-folder 37-26)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO CAROL G. STEBBINGS 1980, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 37-27)
  HOFFMAN, BROWNING, M.D.
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1975-1980, 5 TLS (Box-folder 37-28)
- FELLOWSHIP ANNOUNCEMENT N.D., TMs (P) (Box-folder 37-29)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1980/ca, 2 Reprints (Box-folder 37-30)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1974-1976, 7 TLS (P) (Box-folder 37-31)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL, LETTER, NOTE 1976/ca, AN, TLS (P), TMs (P) (Box-folder 37-32)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1973-1975, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 38-1)
  HOOK, EDWARD W.
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1976, 16 TLS (Box-folder 38-2)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1975, 8 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 38-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS SLIDE AND INSTRUCTIONS N.D., TMs (P), Slide (Box-folder 38-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS AND PAMPHLETS 1973-1974, 6 Reprints/Pamphlets (Box-folder 38-5)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1973, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 38-6)
  Human Dimensions in Medical Education
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1972-1973, 6 TLS (Box-folder 38-7)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1974, 6 TMS (Box-folder 38-8)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, 14 TLS/ALS/TM (P) (Box-folder 38-9)
- CHERYL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, 2 ALS (Box-folder 38-10)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE AND RECEIPT 1972/ca, TN, Printed Form (Box-folder 38-11)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1973/ca, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 38-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS LETTERS 1973/ca, 2 ALS (P) (Box-folder 38-13)
- WORKSHOP ANNOUNCEMENTS 1974-1975, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 38-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS PROGRAM PAMPHLETS 1973-1976, 11 Pamphlets (Box-folder 38-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1958-1974, 5 Reprints (Box-folder 38-16)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1966-1977, 14 TL (CC) (Box-folder 38-17)
  I File